337955194@qq.com 13158913239

# Min Yang

# **English**

Haikou

#### **SUMMARY**

Once worked as English teaching assistant in a training institution. Have a good command of the content and pace of the class, and can clearly understand the important and difficult points of classroom teaching. Treat students more patient, have affinity. Serious and responsible to work, hard-working, good at learning.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Teaching assistant

Chongqing Yiweiyi education technology co. LTD, Chongqing

Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

- Assist the teaching department to ensure the normal operation of teaching
- Organize students to make independent learning plans, give feedback on self-study records, and check students' course learning status
- Send and receive student data, notice, letter, organize teaching tracking
- Collect student information and communicate effectively

### **English volunteer**

ShineWing accounting firm, Chonging

Oct 2018 - Oct 2018

Served as a volunteer English interpreter at ShineWing international partnership meeting, visited and explained to foreign partners.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor degree**

Chongging university of education, Chongging

2016 - Current

- 1. Mandarin level 2 certificate
- 2. Certificate of cet-4 and cet-6
- 3. Primary school teacher certificate
- 4. School scholarship

## **ADVANTAGES**

Like children, do things with patience and focus, good personality, positive and so on.